Office of the Vice-President, Research fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Office of the Vice-President, Research fonds
1968 - 2006, predominant 1968 - 2000
F-86
5.38 m of textual records
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
The Office of the Vice-President, Research has undergone name changes that include: Office of the Vice-President, Research and Information systems (1985 - 1990) Office of the Vice-President, Research (1990 - )
Financial assistance for the arrangement and description of the records and production of the finding aid was generously provided by the Office of the Vice-President, Research.
Office of the Vice-President, Research
The Office of the Vice-President Research/Information Systems was officially established on September 1, 1985. Prior to this, the Associate Vice-President, Academic, John Webster was responsible for research and information systems related tasks and correspondence.
Reporting directly to the President, the new Vice-President, Tom Calvert, supervised the Instructional Media Centre, Library, Computing Services, Animal Care Facility, and University Archives. Between 1986 and 1993 he also supervised Research Services, ‘SFU Ventures’, and the University/Industry Liaison Office. In November 1988 Calvert was also appointed the Director of the Industry/Liaison Office and held both positions until August 1990. That same year the name Office of Vice-President, Research/Information Systems was changed to Office of the Vice-President, Research.
On September 1, 1990 William Leiss replaced Calvert as the new Vice-President Research. Leiss served as Vice-President until August 1993 when he was replaced by Bruce Clayman. Clayman served as the Acting Vice-President, Research until 1994 when he was officially appointed as Vice-President, Research. In 1994 Clayman also began serving as the Dean of Graduate Studies where he handled related policy matters and external relations for the graduate studies program. Clayman served as Vice-President, Research until August 2004 and during this time continued to supervise the Library, Research Services, University/Industry Liaison Office, Animal Care Facility, the Radiation Safety Office, and the Office of Research Ethics. In September 2004, Mario Pinto was appointed as the new Vice-President, Research.
The mission of the Office of the Vice-President, Research is to act as an advocate for university research and guide policy development at the university, provincial and national levels. The Office assists faculty members in applying for research grants at all levels of funding. In September of every year the Office participates in the university orientation program coordinated by the Office of the Vice-President, Academic.
The Vice-President chairs the President's Research Grant Committee and is President of SF Univentures, a for-profit company owned by SFU and used to commercialize research results. The Vice-President also serves on numerous boards and committees in the research community.
The Office of the Vice-President, Research has produced a series of publications through the years reporting on research projects at the university including "Simon Fraser University Research" and "SFU Research Matters." The Office publishes a newsletter three times a year called "Research Links" and supports the distribution of "Research Partners" by the University/Industry Liaison Office.
published
Full
Published
Title of the fonds is based on the name of its creator.
The fonds consists of records relating to the administration of the Office of the Vice-President, Research. Activities, topics and events documented include correspondence with university departments, research centres and institutes, and members of the larger university community on research-related topics; liaison with the local and national research industry and the government; reports on SFU-based research projects and initiatives; and financial records including budget reports and grant applications. Also included are records of the Vice-President's involvement on university, industry and government committees. The fonds also has records relating to Bruce Clayman's term as both the Vice-President, Research and Dean of Graduate Studies.
The types of documents include meeting agendas, minutes and supporting papers; correspondence and reports; annual reports; budgets and financial working papers; contracts; and publications including newsletters, posters, brochures and directories.
The material was arranged by the archivist. Within each series the records have been arranged chronologically.
Pinto, Mario; Calvert, Thomas W.; Leiss, William; Clayman, Bruce P.
The records were transferred to the Archives through the regular application of university Records Retention Schedules and Disposal Authorities (RRSDAs).
As of March 2007, all accessions have been processed. Further accruals are expected.
For other material relating to the Dean of Graduate Studies please see the finding aid (F-225). For records relating to research iniatives and projects on campus, see the finding aids for the appropriate academic department. For records relating to the Tri-University Meson Facility (TRIUMF), please contact the TRIUMF research laboratory at the University of British Columbia.
Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked "pending review" must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release and, as a result of the review, access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
File lists are available.
An "Access Points Index" is available for this fonds in Appendix A.
- Correspondence, 1968 - 2000; F-86-1; 2.86 m of textual records
  published
  Series consists of administrative correspondence between the Vice-President, Research and university departments on research-related issues, policy development, and proposals; local companies and international research organizations; and government ministries. Also included are Bruce Clayman's correspondence records when he held the joint position of Vice-President, Research/Dean of Graduate Studies.
  Document types include correspondence and working papers, reports, minutes, and publications.
  - Dean's Office Administrative correspondence, 1980 - 1996; F-86-1-1; 7 cm of textual records
    Records in this sub-series dating prior to 1985 were previously held by the Associate Vice-President, Academic and inherited by the Office of the Vice-President, Research after it was established in 1985.
    - Office for Applied Research and Business Development, [198-?]; F-86-1-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 86-1)
      Textual records
      Pending review
      Creator's original file classification code: R.3.6.3.
    - Space for Research, 1984; F-86-1-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 86-1)
      Creator's original file classification code: R.3.6.2.
    - Re-organization of VP Academic and Graduate Studies Dept., 1984 - 1985; F-86-1-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 86-1)
      Creator's original file classification code: R.3.6.4.
    - Staff for establishment of University/Industry Liaison Office, 1985 - 1986; F-86-1-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 86-1)
      Creator's original file classification code: RD.04.
    - Open House at UBC, 1987; F-86-1-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 86-1)
      Creator's original file classification code: F.4.1.
    - Office reorganization, 1991; F-86-1-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 86-1)
    - VPR: Search Committee, 1995 - 1996; F-86-1-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 86-1)
  - University correspondence, 1968 - 1999; F-86-1-2; 2.13 m of textual records
    - General correspondence, 1968 - 1999; F-86-1-2-1; 68 cm of textual records
      National Research Council; Science Council of B.C.; Royal Society of Canada; Concordia University; Open Learning Agency; Forest Renewal B.C.; North Atlantic Treaty Organization
      - Copyright policy, 1968 - 1985; F-86-1-2-1-1 (Archival box - standard 86-1)
        Creator's original file classification code: 3.3.3.13.60.
      - Research Groups - policy AD 35 and AD9-24, 1978 - 1982; F-86-1-2-1-2 (Archival box - standard 86-1)
        Creator's original file classification code: 3.4.2.14.50.
      - Research Policy and procedures (revisions), 1980 - 1986; F-86-1-2-1-3 (Archival box - standard 86-1)
        Creator's original file classification code: R.3.4.2.
      - Slowpoke, 1981; F-86-1-2-1-4 (Archival box - standard 86-1)
      - NRC Lab proposal - Manning, 1982; F-86-1-2-1-5 (Archival box - standard 86-1)
        Creator's original file classification code: R.1.1.5.
      - NRC Laboratory, 1982 - 1983; F-86-1-2-1-6 (Archival box - standard 86-1)
      - IRDC/CIDA/SFU/Thailand, 1983 - 1985; F-86-1-2-1-7 (Archival box - standard 86-2)
        Creator's original file classification code: R.3.9.2.
      - University-Industrial interaction study, 1984; F-86-1-2-1-8 (Archival box - standard 86-2)
      - NSERC/University Industrial programmes, 1984; F-86-1-2-1-9 (Archival box - standard 86-2)
        Creator's original file classification code: R.2.1.1(b).
      - McGinnis CHAIR in Human Rights, 1984; F-86-1-2-1-10 (Archival box - standard 86-2)
        Creator's original file classification code: R.2.1.11.
      - J.S. Woodsworth CHAIR in Humanities, 1984 - 1985; F-86-1-2-1-11 (Archival box - standard 86-2)
        Creator's original file classification code: R.2.1.12.
      - NSERC/University Industrial Research Professorships/CHAIRS, 1984 - 1985; F-86-1-2-1-12 (Archival box - standard 86-2)
        Creator's original file classification code: R.2.1.1.
      - Bridge to the Future Campaign, 1984 - 1989; F-86-1-2-1-13 (Archival box - standard 86-2)
      - SFU Village, 1986; F-86-1-2-1-14 (Archival box - standard 86-2)
      - Engineering Science Student Co., vol. 1, 1987 - 1990; F-86-1-2-1-15 (Archival box - standard 86-2)
      - Engineering Science Student Co., vol. 2, 1987 - 1990; F-86-1-2-1-16 (Archival box - standard 86-2)
      - SFU Press, 1989 - 1990; F-86-1-2-1-17 (Archival box - standard 86-2)
      - Conflict of Interest Inquiry, vol. 1, 1989 - 1993; F-86-1-2-1-18 (Archival box - standard 86-3)
      - Conflict of Interest Inquiry, vol. 2, 1989 - 1993; F-86-1-2-1-19 (Archival box - standard 86-3)
      - Conflict of Interest Inquiry, vol. 3, 1989 - 1993; F-86-1-2-1-20 (Archival box - standard 86-3)
      - Conflict of Interest Inquiry, vol. 4, 1989 - 1993; F-86-1-2-1-21 (Archival box - standard 86-3)
      - Conflict of Interest Inquiry, vol. 5, 1989 - 1993; F-86-1-2-1-22 (Archival box - standard 86-3)
      - Conflict of Interest Inquiry, vol. 6, 1989 - 1993; F-86-1-2-1-23 (Archival box - standard 86-3)
      - Strategic plan, 1990 - 1991; F-86-1-2-1-24 (Archival box - standard 86-4)
      - SFU: Meekison Report, 1992; F-86-1-2-1-25 (Archival box - standard 86-4)
      - Intellectual Property Policy, 1992 - 1994; F-86-1-2-1-26 (Archival box - standard 86-4)
      - VPR: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1992 - 1994; F-86-1-2-1-27 (Archival box - standard 86-4)
      - Eco Research Tricouncil Secretariat, 1992 - 1994; F-86-1-2-1-28 (Archival box - standard 86-4)
      - Science Council of B.C. general correspondence, 1992 - 1995; F-86-1-2-1-29 (Archival box - standard 86-4)
      - B.C. Atlas project, 1992 - 1995; F-86-1-2-1-30 (Archival box - standard 86-5)
      - VRP: mentoring program, 1993 - 1994; F-86-1-2-1-31 (Archival box - standard 86-5)
      - VRP: Excellence in Research Award, 1993 - 1995; F-86-1-2-1-32 (Archival box - standard 86-5)
      - Korea and SFU, 1993 - 1995; F-86-1-2-1-33 (Archival box - standard 86-5)
      - Royal Society of Canada, 1993 - 1998; F-86-1-2-1-34 (Archival box - standard 86-5)
      - Concordia University, 1994; F-86-1-2-1-35 (Archival box - standard 86-5)
      - Policies: Integrity in Research, past drafts, 1994 - 1995; F-86-1-2-1-36 (Archival box - standard 86-5)
      - Misconduct in Research Policy, 1994 - 1995; F-86-1-2-1-37 (Archival box - standard 86-5)
        Creator's original file classification code: R60.01.
      - Policies: Integrity in Research, general, 1994 - 1996; F-86-1-2-1-38 (Archival box - standard 86-5)
      - Tricouncil Presidents Iniative on Integrity in Research, vol. 1, 1994 - 1996; F-86-1-2-1-39 (Archival box - standard 86-5)
      - Tricouncil Presidents Iniative on Integrity in Research, vol. 2, 1994 - 1996; F-86-1-2-1-40 (Archival box - standard 86-6)
      - Policies: Conflict of Interest Policy, 1994 - 1996; F-86-1-2-1-41 (Archival box - standard 86-6)
      - Rehabilitation Science Facility, 1995 - 1996; F-86-1-2-1-42 (Archival box - standard 86-6)
      - Forest Renewal B.C., 1995 - 1996; F-86-1-2-1-43 (Archival box - standard 86-6)
      - Learn Linc., 1996; F-86-1-2-1-44 (Archival box - standard 86-6)
      - Policies: Modem policy, 1996; F-86-1-2-1-45 (Archival box - standard 86-6)
      - Policies: Principal Investigator Fees Policy, 1996; F-86-1-2-1-46 (Archival box - standard 86-6)
      - UniGIS, 1996; F-86-1-2-1-47 (Archival box - standard 86-6)
      - Open Learning Agency, 1996 - 1999; F-86-1-2-1-48 (Archival box - standard 86-6)
      - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1997; F-86-1-2-1-49 (Archival box - standard 86-6)
      - Intl Ctr Criminal Law Criminal Justice Policy, 1997 - 1999; F-86-1-2-1-50 (Archival box - standard 86-6)
      - MPR Teltech Clean Rooms, 1997 - 1999; F-86-1-2-1-51 (Archival box - standard 86-6)
      - Western Economic Diversification, 1998; F-86-1-2-1-52 (Archival box - standard 86-6)
    - Departmental correspondence, 1977 - 1997; F-86-1-2-2; 33 cm of textual records
      Department of Biological Sciences; Department of Chemistry; Department of Physics; Cooperative Education; International Centre
      - Instruction Media Centre review, 1977 - 1988; F-86-1-2-2-1 (Archival box - standard 86-6)
      - Bookstore, 1984 - 1990; F-86-1-2-2-2 (Archival box - standard 86-7)
      - Continuing Studies - Athabaska courses, 1986 - 1989; F-86-1-2-2-3 (Archival box - standard 86-7)
      - Co-Operative Education, vol. 1, 1986 - 1996; F-86-1-2-2-4 (Archival box - standard 86-7)
        Creator's original file classification code: C.6.1.
      - Co-Operative Education, vol. 2, 1986 - 1996; F-86-1-2-2-5 (Archival box - standard 86-7)
      - Instruction Media Centre, vol. 1, 1987 - 1990; F-86-1-2-2-6 (Archival box - standard 86-7)
        Creator's original file classification code: B.2.6.
      - Instruction Media Centre, vol. 2, 1987 - 1990; F-86-1-2-2-7 (Archival box - standard 86-7)
      - International Centre - proposal to establish, 1990 - 1992; F-86-1-2-2-8 (Archival box - standard 86-7)
      - International Centre - correspondence, vol. 1, 1991 - 1993; F-86-1-2-2-9 (Archival box - standard 86-8)
      - International Centre - correspondence, vol. 2, 1991 - 1993; F-86-1-2-2-10 (Archival box - standard 86-8)
      - International Centre - correspondence, vol. 3, 1991 - 1993; F-86-1-2-2-11 (Archival box - standard 86-8)
      - International Centre - correspondence, vol. 4, 1991 - 1993; F-86-1-2-2-12 (Archival box - standard 86-8)
      - International Centre - general information, 1992; F-86-1-2-2-13 (Archival box - standard 86-8)
      - Physics, 1993 - 1996; F-86-1-2-2-14 (Archival box - standard 86-9)
      - Biological Sciences, 1994 - 1996; F-86-1-2-2-15 (Archival box - standard 86-9)
      - Biological Sciences - diving safety, 1994 - 1997; F-86-1-2-2-16 (Archival box - standard 86-9)
      - Chemistry - general, 1995 - 1996; F-86-1-2-2-17 (Archival box - standard 86-9)
    - University/Industry Liaison Office, 1983 - 1996; F-86-1-2-3; 40 cm of textual records
      - Proposal for establishment of University/Industry Liaison Office, vol. 1, 1983 - 1985; F-86-1-2-3-1 (Archival box - standard 86-9)
        Creator's original file classification code: RD.01.
      - Proposal for establishment of University/Industry Liaison Office, vol. 2, 1983 - 1985; F-86-1-2-3-2 (Archival box - standard 86-9)
      - Funding for establishment of University/Industry Liaison Office, 1984 - 1985; F-86-1-2-3-3 (Archival box - standard 86-9)
        Creator's original file classification code: RD.03.
      - Oehlschlager report, 1984 - 1985; F-86-1-2-3-4 (Archival box - standard 86-10)
        Creator's original file classification code: RD.001.
      - Establishment of University/Industry Liaison Office, 1984 - 1986; F-86-1-2-3-5 (Archival box - standard 86-10)
        Creator's original file classification code: RD.02.
      - Progress report, 1985; F-86-1-2-3-6 (Archival box - standard 86-10)
      - 1985/1986 agreement, F-86-1-2-3-7 (Archival box - standard 86-10)
      - U/ILO original proposal - 5 year plan Fed/Prov Sub Agreement on Sci/Tech, 1985 - 1986; F-86-1-2-3-8 (Archival box - standard 86-10)
      - Quarterly meetings SFU/UBC/UVIC/Ministries, 1985 - 1986; F-86-1-2-3-9 (Archival box - standard 86-10)
      - Progress report, vol. 1, 1986; F-86-1-2-3-10 (Archival box - standard 86-10)
      - Progress report, vol. 2, 1986; F-86-1-2-3-11 (Archival box - standard 86-10)
      - Progress report, vol. 3, 1986; F-86-1-2-3-12 (Archival box - standard 86-10)
      - Internal meetings - group/admin, 1986; F-86-1-2-3-13 (Archival box - standard 86-10)
      - Faculty Research Officers, vol. 1, 1986 - 1987; F-86-1-2-3-14 (Archival box - standard 86-11)
        Creator's original file classification code: B.1.
      - Faculty Research Officers, vol. 2, 1986 - 1987; F-86-1-2-3-15 (Archival box - standard 86-11)
      - Triuniversity patent fund, 1986 - 1987; F-86-1-2-3-16 (Archival box - standard 86-11)
      - Budget papers and 1986/1987 agreement, F-86-1-2-3-17 (Archival box - standard 86-11)
      - Progress report, 1986 - 1987; F-86-1-2-3-18 (Archival box - standard 86-11)
      - Special reports, 1986 - 1988; F-86-1-2-3-19 (Archival box - standard 86-11)
      - Progress/year end report, 1986 - 1990; F-86-1-2-3-20 (Archival box - standard 86-11)
      - Business plans, reports and evaluations, 1987; F-86-1-2-3-21 (Archival box - standard 86-11)
      - Progress report, vol. 1, 1987; F-86-1-2-3-22 (Archival box - standard 86-11)
      - Progress report, vol. 2, 1987; F-86-1-2-3-23 (Archival box - standard 86-11)
      - Progress report, vol. 3, 1987; F-86-1-2-3-24 (Archival box - standard 86-11)
      - Progress report, vol. 4, 1987; F-86-1-2-3-25 (Archival box - standard 86-11)
      - Business plan and 1987/1988 agreement, F-86-1-2-3-26 (Archival box - standard 86-12)
      - Year end report, 1987 - 1990; F-86-1-2-3-27 (Archival box - standard 86-12)
      - Progress report, vol. 1, 1988; F-86-1-2-3-28 (Archival box - standard 86-12)
      - Quarterly meeting, 1988; F-86-1-2-3-29 (Archival box - standard 86-12)
      - Progress report, 1989; F-86-1-2-3-30 (Archival box - standard 86-12)
      - U/ILO general, 1995 - 1996; F-86-1-2-3-31 (Archival box - standard 86-12)
      - Western Canadian University Tech Fund (WCUTF), 1996; F-86-1-2-3-32 (Archival box - standard 86-12)
    - Animal Care Facility, 1986 - 1996; F-86-1-2-4; 4 cm of textual records
      - Animal Care Facility, 1986 - 1990; F-86-1-2-4-1 (Archival box - standard 86-12)
        Creator's original file classification code: B.2.1.
      - Animal Care Facility, 1993 - 1996; F-86-1-2-4-2 (Archival box - standard 86-12)
      - Animal Care Facility - CCAC Assessment, 1994 - 1995; F-86-1-2-4-3 (Archival box - standard 86-12)
    - SF Univentures, 1991 - 1997; F-86-1-2-5; 5 cm of textual records
      - SF Univentures, 1991 - 1997; F-86-1-2-5-1 (Archival box - standard 86-13)
      - SF Univentures, 1992; F-86-1-2-5-2 (Archival box - standard 86-13)
      - Kinetic Effects - KERI, 1996; F-86-1-2-5-3 (Archival box - standard 86-13)
    - Computing Services, 1985 - 1990; F-86-1-2-6; 29 cm of textual records
      - Heavy duty computing, 1985; F-86-1-2-6-1 (Archival box - standard 86-13)
      - Computer equipment developments, 1985 - 1986; F-86-1-2-6-2 (Archival box - standard 86-13)
      - Computerization of office systems, 1985 - 1986; F-86-1-2-6-3 (Archival box - standard 86-13)
      - Micro computer usage on campus, 1985 - 1986; F-86-1-2-6-4 (Archival box - standard 86-13)
      - Administrative information systems, 1985 - 1989; F-86-1-2-6-5 (Archival box - standard 86-13)
      - Computing Services, vol. 1, 1985 - 1990; F-86-1-2-6-6 (Archival box - standard 86-14)
      - Computing Services, vol. 2, 1985 - 1990; F-86-1-2-6-7 (Archival box - standard 86-14)
      - Computerization of instruction, 1985 - 1990; F-86-1-2-6-8 (Archival box - standard 86-14)
      - B.C. Net opening, 1986; F-86-1-2-6-9 (Archival box - standard 86-14)
      - Computer networks, 1986 - 1987; F-86-1-2-6-10 (Archival box - standard 86-14)
      - AIS - policy/reports, vol. 1, 1986 - 1989; F-86-1-2-6-11 (Archival box - standard 86-14)
      - AIS - policy/reports, vol. 2, 1986 - 1989; F-86-1-2-6-12 (Archival box - standard 86-14)
      - Supercomputer, vol. 1, 1987 - 1989; F-86-1-2-6-13 (Archival box - standard 86-15)
      - Supercomputer, vol. 2, 1987 - 1989; F-86-1-2-6-14 (Archival box - standard 86-15)
      - Computing Services management meeting, 1989 - 1990; F-86-1-2-6-15 (Archival box - standard 86-15)
      - Ian Williams - for discussion, 1990; F-86-1-2-6-16 (Archival box - standard 86-15)
    - Discovery Enterprises, 1985 - 1992; F-86-1-2-7; 8 cm of textual records
      - Discovery Foundation Board of Directors - general, 1985 - 1991; F-86-1-2-7-1 (Archival box - standard 86-15)
      - Business Plan, 1988 - 1990; F-86-1-2-7-2 (Archival box - standard 86-15)
      - Monthly Trustee reports, 1989 - 1990; F-86-1-2-7-3 (Archival box - standard 86-16)
      - Executive Committee, 1989 - 1992; F-86-1-2-7-4 (Archival box - standard 86-16)
    - Radiation Safety Office, 1992 - 1996; F-86-1-2-8; 2 cm of textual records
      - Radiation Safety office, 1992 - 1996; F-86-1-2-8-1 (Archival box - standard 86-16)
    - Archives, 1982 - 1990; F-86-1-2-9; 7 cm of textual records
      - Archives, vol. 1, 1982 - 1990; F-86-1-2-9-1 (Archival box - standard 86-16)
        Creator's original file classification code: B.2.2.
      - Archives, vol. 2, 1982 - 1990; F-86-1-2-9-2 (Archival box - standard 86-16)
      - Archives, vol. 3, 1982 - 1990; F-86-1-2-9-3 (Archival box - standard 86-16)
      - Archives and Records Management Committee, 1986 - 1989; F-86-1-2-9-4 (Archival box - standard 86-16)
    - Library, 1985 - 1996; F-86-1-2-10; 18 cm of textual records
      - Library - GEAC, 1985 - 1989; F-86-1-2-10-1 (Archival box - standard 86-17)
      - Library, vol. 1, 1987 - 1990; F-86-1-2-10-2 (Archival box - standard 86-17)
        Creator's original file classification code: B.2.7.
      - Library, vol. 2, 1987 - 1990; F-86-1-2-10-3 (Archival box - standard 86-17)
      - Ted Dobb - for discussion, 1987 - 1990; F-86-1-2-10-4 (Archival box - standard 86-17)
      - Library Management Group, 1987 - 1990; F-86-1-2-10-5 (Archival box - standard 86-17)
      - Ministry of Skills Training and Labour: Innovation Fund, 1994; F-86-1-2-10-6 (Archival box - standard 86-17)
      - Aragon collection, 1994 - 1995; F-86-1-2-10-7 (Archival box - standard 86-18)
      - Cancopy Agreement, 1994 - 1996; F-86-1-2-10-8 (Archival box - standard 86-18)
      - Book robot, 1995 - 1996; F-86-1-2-10-9 (Archival box - standard 86-18)
      - General, 1996; F-86-1-2-10-10 (Archival box - standard 86-18)
  - B. Clayman Vice-President, Research/Dean of Graduate Studies records, 1984 - 2000; F-86-1-3; 18 cm of textual records